Flap your wings and fly straight towards your dream
はばたけ 夢に向かってまっすぐ
not tomorrow, but right now
明日じゃなくていますぐ
Everyone, move on to the next shining stage, let’s fly away!
みんな 輝くステ — ジ 進め fly away！
When you put several passionate vows together
熱い誓いを 幾つも重ねたなら
they create enough power to open the door to a huge chance
でっかいチャンスの扉さえ 開けるパワ — になるよ
During tough times, when I see my friends’ faces, even if
苦しい時に 仲間の顔見るたび
I’m close to breaking down, it seems like light will shine on me
壊れてしまいそうな気持ちに ヒカリが射す気がした
Cheering each other up through text messages
携帯メ — ルでね 励まし合ったメッセ — ジ
Because I received lots of energy and courage from them
元気勇気いっぱい もらったから
Flap your wings and fly straight towards your dream
はばたけ 夢に向かってまっすぐ
not tomorrow, but right now
明日じゃなくていますぐ
because we don’t want to just stand around and wait
だって待ってなんか いられない
It’s a storm of shining hopes, with our strong bonds
輝く希望の嵐 強い絆で
Let’s release our shine and aim for the best future
キラメキ放ち 最高の未来 目指そうよ
Even if it seems small, our dream is big
ちっちゃく見えても 夢はおっきいから
With a heart unfearful of failures
失敗怖れない心で
I looked up at the faraway sky
高い空を見上げた
Even with these small wings, I carry big ideals
ちっちゃい翼で おっきな理想抱え
But sometimes I’ll act like a spoiled little sister and rely on my friends
ときには妹の気分で 仲間に甘えちゃった
When I wrote my first blog entry
初めてブログを 書いた時に手にした
I got my hands on lots of treasures, and I still continue to now
宝物はいっぱい 今もあるよ
Flap your wings and fly straight towards your dream
はばたけ 夢に向かってまっすぐ
not tomorrow, but right now
明日じゃなくていますぐ
Turn your strong desires into a shining gust of wind
強い願いを光る風にして
Let it blow away all of your fears, and with your own smile
緊張なんか吹き飛ばし 自分の笑顔で
always stay strong, look ahead and fly up high
いつでも強く 前を向いて高く飛んで行こう
Flap your wings and fly straight towards your dream
はばたけ 夢に向かってまっすぐ
not tomorrow, but right now
明日じゃなくていますぐ
because we don’t want to just stand around and wait
だって待ってなんかいられない
It’s a storm of shining hopes, with our strong bonds
輝く希望の嵐 強い絆で
Let’s release our shine and aim
キラメキ放ち 最高の
For the future, now fly straight towards your dream
未来へ 夢に向かってまっすぐ
not tomorrow, but right now
明日じゃなくていますぐ
Turn your strong desires into a shining gust of wind
強い願いを光る風にして
Let it blow away all of your fears, and with your own smile
緊張なんか吹き飛ばし 自分の笑顔で
always stay strong, look ahead and fly up high
いつでも強く 前を向いて高く飛んで行こう